Guide to the Anne Law Colville, Album.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
[Album]
1840-1840
OSBORN D64
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.21
(1 volume)
Autograph MSS. Collection of signatures, mostly cut, of "Distinguished Individuals"; the collection is arranged in the following categories: Royal Family, Military, Naval, Statesmen and Diplomatists, Divines, Peers and M.P.'s, Lawyers, Scientists, Artists, Literary, etc.
Colville, Anne (Law) Colville, Baroness, d. 1852
Immediate Source of Acquisition
For provenance information, consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The following finding aid is a partial inventory of the contents of Osborn d64. This list was reformatted from previously existing cataloging.
Autographs -- Great Britain; Colville, Anne (Law) Colville, Baroness, d. 1852
- Osborn d64
  - BERTHIER, LOUIS ALEXANDRE, PRINCE DE NEUCHATEL ET WAGRAM
    - ALS to an unidentified recipient, 1811 Oct 26 (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Rotterdam
      1 p.; 21 x 18 cm.
      d.64/14
  - BURKE, EDMUND, 1729?-1797
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1783 Jan 29 (Box 1)
      London
      1 p.; 10 x 16 cm.
      d.64/27v
  - DUMOURIEZ, CHARLES FRANCOIS DUPERRIER, 1739-1823
    - Document, signed, 1793 Feb 17 (Box 1)
      n.p.
      1 p.; 24 x 20 cm.
      Military order.
      d.64/13
  - ERNEST AUGUSTUS, KING OF HANOVER, 1771-1851
    - ALS to an unidentified recipient, 1832 Jul 29 (Box 1)
      St. James Palace
      1 p.; 11 x 11 cm.
      d.64/5
  - FRANKLIN, BENJAMIN, 1706-1790
    - ALS (fragment) spurious, presumably to David Hartley (1705-1757), n.d. (Box 1)
      1 p.; 9 x 14 cm.
      d.64/25
  - MATHIAS, THOMAS JAMES, 1754?-1835
    - ALS to [?William Towry] Law (1809-), 1822 Mar 16 (Box 1)
      Pizzo-Falcone
      1 p.; 12 x 10 cm.
      d.64/68v
  - WALPOLE, HORACE, 4TH EARL OF ORFORD, 1717-1797
    - Cover, addressed to Captain Waldegrave [?William Waldegrave, 1st baron Radstock (1753-1825)], 1789 Oct 22 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 10 x 11 cm.
      d.64/71